{
    "subject": "resource/Teenage_Kicks",
    "predicate": "property/genre",
    "object": "resource/Punk_rock",
    "human_readable": "The genre of Teenage Kicks is Punk rock.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9646100401878357,
            "question": "Is Teenage Kicks considered Punk rock?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7812020778656006,
            "question": "What genre of music is Teenage Kicks?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7248032093048096,
            "question": "Can you give an example of a song from the Punk rock genre besides Teenage Kicks?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.464326411485672,
            "question": "Can you name a musical genre similar to Punk rock?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3673875331878662,
            "question": "What are some characteristics of Punk rock music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3491796553134918,
            "question": "Are there any famous Punk rock bands?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28282490372657776,
            "question": "What is the cultural impact of Punk rock music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26931819319725037,
            "question": "What are some common themes in Punk rock lyrics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23895688354969025,
            "question": "Where did Punk rock music originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23486872017383575,
            "question": "When did Punk rock music emerge?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The genre of Teenage Kicks is Punk rock.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1127_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Punk rock music originate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1127_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes in Punk rock lyrics?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1127_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the cultural impact of Punk rock music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1127_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1127_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1127_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1127_146.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1127_150.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1127_153.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1127_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1127_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1127_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1127_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1127_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports that the genre of Teenage Kicks is indeed Punk rock. The documents repeatedly mention the band's association with the punk movement, their raw and energizing music, and their unrelenting intensity and shameless attitude, all of which are consistent with the characteristics of a punk rock band."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe provided documents clearly indicate that Teenage Kicks is a punk rock band from Toronto, Canada. This information supports the statement that the genre of Teenage Kicks is punk rock."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}